hey everyone Caff man here today we're
going to be going over the monster Rio
Punch coming right
[Music]
up hello again everyone thank you so
much for joining me today I really do
appreciate it Happy New Year to everyone
in what better way to start the new year
off them with a brand new drink and to
be honest this drink actually hasn't
been released yet it will probably be
coming out within the next few weeks but
it was announced last year as being a
first quarter release for monster and a
huge shout out and thank you goes to
Cole for sending me these Monster drinks
and Rain drinks early I really do
appreciate it because of him I can get
you guys nice and early reviews so you
know whether to buy it when it comes out
or not not like you're not going to buy
it it's monster but what exactly is a
Rio punch uh listen you can go down a
rabbit hole when you try and find out
when you Google what is Rio punch Google
what's Rio punch did I activate some of
your devices yes that's fun that's fun
but there's tons of information out
there and since I don't exactly know you
know they got pictures on there and who
knows if they're going truck tropical if
they're going Rio de Janeiro if they're
going for like a party or festive type
can it's a very busy looking can we'll
look at that in a second I did find
something that is actually a company
it's actually called Rio is the name of
the company I believe it's based out of
Vietnam and it's called Rio juice and
it's got mango passion fruit papaya
guava pineapple and punch it says it has
punch in there so I'm guessing it means
fruit punch so this drink could have all
that stuff or it could just be another
tropical mix from Monster it is part of
their juice line and let's go ahead and
take a look at some of the numbers
before we taste it out and taking a
quick look at the can you're going to
see that this has 140 calories 180 mg of
sodium and 36 G of carbs coming from 33
g of sugar what's important to note
there is that um most of the Juice
drinks they usually have different sugar
counts some of the Juice flavors have up
to like 54 g of sugar but I've seen
others in the high 30s some in the 40s
as well so I guess it's really a matter
of the flavor they're trying to go with
because none of the drinks in the juice
line are consistent with the amount of
sugar that they they put in there which
is perfectly fine there's nothing wrong
with that but usually when you have a
drink line usually the numbers are
pretty standard across the board for the
line but they're not doing that for the
sugar and since I do know a lot of
people watch their sugar they watch
their carbs they want to know how much
is in these drinks and this one is a
little bit lighter than most of the
Juice drinks that they have at 33 g of
sugar when it comes to your vitamins
you're getting the same amount of B
vitamins that you always get from these
drinks and because it is named juice
there is actually a little bit of juice
they're giving you 2% juice in this
drink so not much juice at all but they
got to give you a little bit if they're
going to name it juice 160 Mig of
caffeine in this 16 o can let's taste it
out and here's the
can little bit festive over
here then over
here go that
[Music]
statue of course you guys all know where
that statue is from so yeah they are
going for a Rio de Janeiro kind of feel
to it still doesn't explain what flavor
exactly that it is just the theme that
they're going for for so why not go
ahead let's just taste it
out ooh look at
that that definitely gives me that
tropical vibe that gives me that guava
kind of feel mhm passion fruit give a
little sniff give a little sniff taste
sniff taste sniff
[Music]
test interesting interesting definitely
seems tropical to me been a fan of guava
drinks and stuff maybe a little papaya
in there too definitely got some red 40
in there too yeah yeah can smell that
red
[Music]
all right so for your carbonation I'm
not sure if it's because it's a sale
sample or not but the carbonation does
seem to be a little bit lighter I'm
going to say it's like a medium
carbonation for your sweetness you're
getting a high sweetness they definitely
give you a lot of sweetness out of here
even though it's only got the 33 g of
sugar which is a lot it still tastes
sweeter than some of those ones that can
be at 54 and it's because they also have
other sweeteners in there such as ccos
and a so they can make the sweetness
pretty much whatever they want and for
your flavor profile I am also going to
say that is a high flavor profile and my
goodness that's a good drink that's
that's a I I I haven't I haven't really
loved many of the Juice drinks that they
came out with uh not just because of the
sugar but just the flavors in general
mango Loco was the exception that was
amazing I like the original chaos
chaotic that came out after it not so
much and not knowing what Rio punch was
going to be going into it I was
skeptical but man that is really really
really really good and uh what's the
flavors uh you definitely get the
tropical feel from it and we're not
talking your standard typical tropical
punch fruit punch kind of flavor you're
getting some really exotic fruits in
here and I say really exotic fruits they
might not be exotic we hear from but I'm
definitely getting a mango guava uh
papaya out of it maybe even a little bit
of touch of kiwi in there and even maybe
maybe on the back end maybe a touch a
touch of pineapple but it's really being
overpowered by a lot of those other
fruits in there and uh it's really
really good and as I was drinking it I'm
like man this reminds me of something it
almost reminds me of like a tropical
like candy kind of flavor like it's got
this sweetness to it where it's like ooh
I remember tasting a candy at some point
like that and not a candy drink I'm
talking like an actual candy like I ate
Candy I don't know what it was but I
think they put it in the can but it's
interesting that you know you're getting
this tropical feel out of it you're not
getting much acidity usually when it
comes to tropical fruit or acidic fruits
you get a high acidity from them but
you're not getting much I don't taste
much Orange in here I don't taste a lot
of the pineapple and whatever fruits
they're using they're not overly acidic
fruits and if they are they're cutting
back on it with a lot of sweetness and
if anything I'm going to go back in from
the can a lot of people say my pores
make it different but eh
whatever I definitely get a candy Vibe
out of it just a light candy Vibe which
is odd but not bad but the closest that
I can relate it to is is one of my other
favorite drinks from Pure zero
Rockstar and that's like the tmgs
Tangerine mango guava strawberry this
definitely doesn't have the Tangerine
flavor in there sort of like they took
the Tangerine out and they given you a
good mango guava maybe just a touch of
strawberry but like I said I think
they're giving you some great flavors in
there I know I'm a big fan of mango and
guava flavors they toss a little
pineapple in there you toss a little
kiwi and you got a great combination mix
of flavors so yeah that's just just has
really good so so let's go ahead let's
put this on the Caff man rating chart
see where it's going to go going to rate
it against some other Tropicals I'll
probably toss in some other flavors too
because like I said it's not strictly a
tropical it's definitely a unique take
on what a tropical could be with the
different flavors they're mixing in
there but we are starting off the year
strong and we are starting off with a
9.5 from monster with their juice I
think that's the highest rated juice or
maybe the maybe the mango Loco might be
higher but it doesn't really matter at a
99.5 you got an amazing drink on your
hands great way to start the year thank
you again to Cole for sending me this
drink I do appreciate it leave me a
comment down below what drink you're
most looking forward to this year and if
you can't wait to get your hands on this
Rio punch if you're interested in my
review on the original Monster juice
line you can check out that video right
there I've reviewed every monster juice
after that so be sure to check out my
channel for those and if you missed my
top 20 of 2023 be sure to check out that
video right there also be sure to check
out Caff 1.com to find out how to save
money on energy drinks using my coupon
codes and affiliate links and until next
time have yourselves a great
day or night